<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kanagram.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kanagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKanagramxx</name>
  <summary>Letter Order Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc d'ordenació de lletres</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc d'ordenació de lletres</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kirjainten järjestyspeli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu sur l'ordre des lettres</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Letters ordenen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo de ordenação de letras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Гра з впорядкування літер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxLetter Order Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Kanagram is a game based on anagrams of words: the puzzle is solved when the letters of the scrambled word are put back in the correct order. There is no limit on either time taken, or the amount of attempts to solve the word. It features several included word lists, a hints-and-cheats help system, a word list editor, and allows for updating and distributing wordlists via KNewStuff. The interface is scalable and appropriate for children.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kanagram és un joc basat en anagrames de paraules: el trencaclosques es resol quan les lletres de la paraula barrejada es col·loquen en l'ordre correcte. No hi ha cap límit en el temps, o en el nombre d'intents per resoldre la paraula. Inclou diverses llistes de paraules, un sistema d'ajuda de consells i trampes, un editor de llistes de paraules, i permet l'actualització i distribució de llistes de paraules via el KNewStuff. La interfície és escalable i adequada a la canalla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Kanagram és un joc basat en anagrames de paraules: el trencaclosques es resol quan les lletres de la paraula barrejada es col·loquen en l'orde correcte. No hi ha cap límit en el temps, o en el nombre d'intents per resoldre la paraula. Inclou diverses llistes de paraules, un sistema d'ajuda de consells i trampes, un editor de llistes de paraules, i permet l'actualització i distribució de llistes de paraules via el KNewStuff. La interfície és escalable i adequada a la canalla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kanagram on anagrammeihin perustuva peli: peli on ratkaistu, kun sanan sekoitetut kirjaimet on laitettu takaisin oikeille paikoilleen. Peli ei rajoita ratkaisemiseen kuluvaa aikaa eikä ratkaisuyrityksiä. Peliin kuuluu useita sanastoja, vihjeet sekä huijaamismahdollisuus ja sanastojen muokkaus. Sanastoja voi myös päivittää ja jakaa verkkoon KNewStuffin välityksellä. Käyttöliittymä on skaalautuva ja sopii lapsille.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kanagram est un jeu construit sur des anagrammes de mots : le puzzle est résolu quand les lettres mélangées d'un mot sont remise dans le bon ordre. Il n'y a pas de limite de temps ou de nombre de tentatives pour résoudre un mot. Il intègre un nombre important de listes de mots, un système de trucs-et-astuces pour aider, un éditeur de liste de mots et permet la distribution de vos listes grâce à KNewStuff. L'interface peut changer d'échelle et est approprié pour les enfants.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kanagram is een spel gebaseerd op anagrammen van woorden: de puzzel is opgelost wanneer de letters van het door elkaar gegooide woord terug zijn geplaatst in de juiste volgorde. Er is geen limiet aan ofwel de genomen tijd of het aantal pogingen om het woord op te lossen. Het biedt verschillende meegeleverde woordlijsten, een tips-en-vals-spelen helpsysteem, een bewerker van woordlijsten en maakt het mogelijk woordlijsten bij te werken en te verspreiden via KNewStuff. Het interface is schaalbaar en geschikt voor kinderen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kanagram é um jogo baseado em anagramas de palavras: o puzzle é solucionado quando as letras da palavra embaralhada forem colocadas na ordem correta. Não existe nenhum limite de tempo ou quantidade de tentativas de resolução da palavra. Oferece diversas listas de palavras já incluídas, um sistema de ajuda por dicas e truques, um editor de listas de palavras, assim como a atualização e distribuição das listas de palavras através do KNewStuff. A interface é ajustável e apropriada para crianças.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KAnagram — це гра, що заснована на розгадуванні анаграм: загадку буде розгадано, якщо розташувати переплутані літери слова у правильному порядку. Обмежень на час розв’язання немає, так само як і на кількість спроб вгадати слово. До пакунка KAnagram вже включено декілька словників підготованих для гри, але набагато більше таких словників ви можете знайти у інтернеті. У програмі передбачено систему підказок, редактор списків слів. Інтерфейс програми є масштабованим та адаптованим для дітей.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKanagram is a game based on anagrams of words: the puzzle is solved when the letters of the scrambled word are put back in the correct order. There is no limit on either time taken, or the amount of attempts to solve the word. It features several included word lists, a hints-and-cheats help system, a word list editor, and allows for updating and distributing wordlists via KNewStuff. The interface is scalable and appropriate for children.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://edu.kde.org/kanagram/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kanagram</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdeedu/kanagram/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kanagram.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kanagram</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
